Inventory of O.41 - Collection of Lists and Documentation Regarding Those Who Perished and Those Who Were Persecuted During the Holocaust Period O.41
O.41 - Collection of Lists and Documentation Regarding Those Who Perished and Those Who Were Persecuted During the Holocaust Period
- Notifications of the Dutch Red Cross of the deprtation of Van Thijn family, 24/09/1957-24/09/1957; 6 Official documentation Letter Record of deportees Record of survivors xerox; O.41/255
  Deportation of Jews; Amsterdam,Noordholland,<>,The Netherlands
  The materials were transferred to Yad Vashem by ון טין קטרינה
  Notifications of the Dutch Red Cross of the deprtation of Van Thijn family.
- List of inmates, most of them Jews from Vilna, who perished in Dautmergen camp, 1944-1945, date empty; 8 List of murdered persons List of camp inmates Typewritten copy; O.41/215
  Dautmergen,Camp; Vilna,Wilno,Wilno,Poland
  The materials were transferred to Yad Vashem by ע"י אברמסקי עירית
  List of inmates, most of them Jews from Vilna, who perished in Dautmergen camp, 1944-1945
- List of Jews deported from Ozarow, 22/10/1942; along with the list are their applications for emigration permits, 1938, Deportes d`Ozarow, woiewodie de Kielce (Pologne) le 22/10/1942; 1938-1938; 77 List of deportees Personal documents Map Typewritten Original and Xerox; O.41/242
  Ozarow,Opatow,Kielce,Poland
  The materials were transferred to Yad Vashem by אדלר הנרי
  List of Jews deported from Ozarow, 22/10/1942; along with the list are their applications for emigration permits, 1938 Applications for emigration permits of Jewish residents of Ozarow presented to the Polish authorities, based on the submission of their identity cards, 1938. According to the testimony of the submitter of this information, Henri Adler from Ozarow, all of the applicants perished in Treblinka during the Holocaust.
- List of Jews from Gleiwitz who were deported to extermination camps, 1942, and reports prepared by the Staatspolizeistelle in Oppeln regarding the escape of Jews, 1943-1944, 1991-1991; 9 Article Reports List of deportees List of persecuted persons xerox; O.41/237
  Gleiwitz,Oppeln,Silesia (Upper),Germany; Oppeln,Oppeln,Silesia (Upper),Germany
  The materials were transferred to Yad Vashem by Prof. Alfred Konieczny
  List of Jews from Gleiwitz who were deported to extermination camps, 1942, and reports prepared by the Staatspolizeistelle in Oppeln regarding the escape of Jews, 1943-1944 - List of Jews from Gleiwitz who were deported to extermination camps, 1942; - Reports prepared by the Staatspolizeistelle in Oppeln, regarding the escape of Jews, 1943-1944; Included in the file: - Brief survey of the deportation of Jews from Upper Silesia.
  - List of Jews from Gliwice who were deported to the death camps, 1942, Lista imienna niemieckich Żidów deportowanych z Gliwic do obozów zaglady w 1942; 1991-1991; 6 List of deportees; O.41/237.1
    Gliwice,Oppeln,Silesia (Upper),Germany
    List of Jews from Gliwice who were deported to the death camps, 1942
    The list/s contain approximately 578 names
  - Reports prepared by the Staatspolizeistelle in Oppeln regarding the escape of Jews, 1943-1944, 06/11/1943-05/05/1944; 2 Reports Record of persecuted persons; O.41/237.2
    Oppeln,Oppeln,Silesia (Upper),Germany
    Reports prepared by the Staatspolizeistelle in Oppeln regarding the escape of Jews, 1943-1944
- "Le Chemin de fer du diable" ("The Devil's Railroad") by Hendrik Ernst, regarding the role of the Reichsbahndirektion (RBD) Saarbrücken railroad company during World War II; research published, 2004, Le chemin de fer du diable; 2004-2004; 138 List of deportees List of murdered persons List of survivors Study Photograph Map xerox File; O.41/945
  Deportation trains; Alsace Lorraine Region,<>,<>,France; Saarbruecken,Saar,Saar,Germany
  The materials were transferred to Yad Vashem by Ernst Hendrik
  "Le Chemin de fer du diable" ("The Devil's Railroad") by Hendrik Ernst, regarding the role of the Reichsbahndirektion (RBD) Saarbrücken railroad company during World War II; research published, 2004
  - List of residents of Alsace and Lorraine who were deported to various camps, and their fate, prepared, 2004, 2004-2004; 43 List of deportees List of murdered persons List of survivors; O.41/945.1
    Alsace Lorraine Region,<>,<>,France
    List of residents of Alsace and Lorraine who were deported to various camps, and their fate, prepared, 2004
  - List of Jews from Sarreguemines who were deported and perished, Juifs de Sarreguemines morts en deportation; 2004-2004; 3 List of deportees List of murdered persons; O.41/945.2
    Sarreguemines,Moselle,<>,France
    List of Jews from Sarreguemines who were deported and perished
- List of Jews deported from the Lodz Ghetto: the women to Ravensbrueck and the men to Sachsenhausen, 03/11/2004-17/02/2005; 11 Letter List of ghetto inmates List of camp inmates List of survivors xerox; O.41/989
  Lodz,Ghetto,Poland; Ravensbrueck,Camp; Sachsenhausen,Camp,Germany
  The materials were transferred to Yad Vashem by ארגון עובדי כפייה תחת שלטון הנאצים, גרינשטיין דוד, יו"ר
  List of Jews deported from the Lodz Ghetto: the women to Ravensbrueck and the men to Sachsenhausen
  The list/s contain approximately 427 names
- List of residents from Kladno who were persecuted and those who perished, published in the journal of the Kladno Historical Museum, date empty; The file was created by Vestnik Sladeckova musea v Kladn; 5 List of residents List of persecuted persons List of murdered persons Print; O.41/429
  Kladno,Kladno,Bohemia,Czechoslovakia
  The material was aquired by Yad Vashem from STATNI OKRESNI ARCHIV, KLADNO, CZECH REPUBLIC
  List of residents from Kladno who were persecuted and those who perished, published in the journal of the Kladno Historical Museum
  The list/s contain approximately 293 names
- Confirmation regarding the death of Majer Pioro, from Paris, who perished in Auschwitz, 15/08/1942, 20/08/1942-20/08/1942; 2 Personal documents Certification Newspaper clippings Record of murdered persons xerox; O.41/448
  Paris,Seine,<>,France; Auschwitz,Camp,Poland
  The materials were transferred to Yad Vashem by זלץ דוד
  Confirmation regarding the death of Majer Pioro, from Paris, who perished in Auschwitz, 15/08/1942
- Partial list of Jews who were murdered, in Gertsa and Gorbova, 07/1941, and documentation regarding their commemoration, Список жертв фашизма, расстрелянных в июле 1941 г. в городе Герцы и село горбова, Черновицкой области; 1977-1990; 8 Official documentation List of murdered persons xerox Typewritten original; O.41/454
  Commemoration; Gertsa,Dorohoi,Moldavia,Romania; Gorbova,Dorohoi,Moldavia,Romania
  The materials were transferred to Yad Vashem by Abraham Zekler
  Partial list of Jews who were murdered, in Gertsa and Gorbova, 07/1941, and documentation regarding their commemoration The file includes correspondence concerning the request to transfer the bones of deceased relatives to Gertsa cemetery and confirmation by the Red Cross in Moscow of the burial of Abraham Zekler's brother.
  - Partial list of Jews who were murdered, in Gertsa and Gorbova, 07/1941, Список жертв фашизма, расстрелянных в июле 1941 г. в городе Герцы и село горбова, Черновицкой области; date empty; 1 List of murdered persons; O.41/454.1
    Gertsa,Dorohoi,Moldavia,Romania; Gorbova,Dorohoi,Moldavia,Romania
    Partial list of Jews who were murdered, in Gertsa and Gorbova, 07/1941 The list was prepared by the submitter, Abraham Zekler.
- Individual page from the Dachau card file with a list of inmates designated for "Nacht und Nebel - N.N."; the list includes the names of inmates intended for death in Dachau, 1944, 1944-1944; 1 List of camp inmates Photocopy; O.41/426
  Dachau,Camp,Germany
  Individual page from the Dachau card file with a list of inmates designated for "Nacht und Nebel - N.N."; the list includes the names of inmates intended for death in Dachau, 1944 "Nacht und Nebel" refers to the "Night and Fog" directive, against opponents of the Nazis in occupied countries.
- Documentation regarding relatives of Kibbutz Givat Oz members who perished in the Holocaust, prepared in their memory by Yosef Shavit, date empty; 13 Record of murdered persons Memoirs Poem/song Stories Print; O.41/441
  Commemoration; Bequeathing the Holocaust; <>,<>,<>,Hungary; Kibbutz Givat Oz,<>,<>,Israel
  Documentation regarding relatives of Kibbutz Givat Oz members who perished in the Holocaust, prepared in their memory by Yosef Shavit
  - List of family members who perished during the Holocaust, prepared by members of Kibbutz Givat Oz, date empty; 6 List of murdered persons; O.41/441.1
    <>,<>,<>,Hungary; Kibbutz Givat Oz,<>,<>,Israel
    List of relatives who perished during the Holocaust, prepared by members of Kibbutz Givat Oz
- List of Jews from the prison Vlilna, Lukiskis who were murdered during the months of July and August, 1941, 01/07/1941-31/08/1942; 13 Official documentation Indictment List of murdered persons xerox; O.41/455
  Mass graves; Lithuanian collaborators; Wilno,Wilno,Wilno,Poland; Niemenczyn,Wilno,Wilno,Poland; Jašiūnai,Wilno,Wilno,Poland; Wilno,Lukiszki,Detention Site,Poland
  The materials were transferred to Yad Vashem by SARA GINAITE-RUBINSONIENE
  List of Jews from the prison Vlilna, Lukiskis who were murdered during the months of July and August, 1941
  - List of Jewish inmates in the Lukiszki prison in Vilna who were executed during 07-08/1941, 25/07/1941-22/08/1941; 4 List of murdered persons; O.41/455.1
    Wilno,Wilno,Wilno,Poland; Wilno,Lukiszki,Detention Site,Poland
    List of Jewish inmates in the Lukiszki prison in Vilna who were executed during 07-08/1941
- Family tree of Yona Fish's family members, date empty; 4 Genealogy Record of murdered persons xerox; O.41/966
  <>,<>,Transylvania,Romania; <>,<>,<>,Hungary
  The materials were transferred to Yad Vashem by פיש יונה
  Family tree of Yona Fish's family members
- Confirmation of the deaths of members of the Blankenstein and Levental families, who perished in the Riga Ghetto, 1941-1943, 09/11/1992-09/11/1992; 1 List of murdered persons xerox; O.41/446
  Riga,Ghetto
  The materials were transferred to Yad Vashem by בלומקין זינאידה
  Confirmation of the deaths of members of the Blankenstein and Levental families, who perished in the Riga Ghetto, 1941-1943 Confirmation from the People's Court in Lattgal, a suburb of Riga, dated 9/11/1992, given to Blumkina Zinaida, as evidence of the deaths of relatives from the Blankenstein and Levental families, who perished in Latvia, 1941-1943.
- List of Jews deported from Ilok, 21/07/1942, 21/07/1942-21/07/1942; 21 List of deportees Typewritten original; O.41/462
  Deportation from Yugoslavia; Ilok,<>,Croatia Srem,Yugoslavia
  The materials were transferred to Yad Vashem by פריד יוסף
  List of Jews deported from Ilok, 21/07/1942
- List of Jews from the Salgotarjan Ghetto who perished during the Holocaust, SALGÓTARJÁNI GETTÓBÓL DEPORTÁLT ÉS MUNKASZOLGÁLATBAN ELPUSZTULT MÁRTÍRJAINK EMLÉKÉRE; date empty; 64 List of murdered persons List of ghetto inmates xerox; O.41/997
  Salgotarjan,Ghetto; Salgotarjan,Nograd,<>,Hungary; Apc,Heves,<>,Hungary; Bocsarlapujto,Nograd,<>,Hungary; Bodony,Nograd,<>,Hungary; Bujak,Nograd,<>,Hungary; Cered,Nograd,<>,Hungary; Csecse,Nograd,<>,Hungary; Ecseg,Nograd,<>,Hungary; Erdokurt,Nograd,<>,Hungary; Homokterenye,Nograd,<>,Hungary; Jobbagyi,Nograd,<>,Hungary; Karancskeszi,Nograd,<>,Hungary; Kallo,Nograd,<>,Hungary; Kisbagyon,Nograd,<>,Hungary; Kisterenye,Nograd,<>,Hungary; Kozard,Nograd,<>,Hungary; Lorinci,Nograd,<>,Hungary; Maconka,Heves,<>,Hungary; Matraballa,Heves,<>,Hungary; Matraderecske,Heves,<>,Hungary; Matranovak,Nograd,<>,Hungary; Nagybatony,Heves,<>,Hungary; Parad,Heves,<>,Hungary; Petervasara,Heves,<>,Hungary; Putnok,Gomor es Kishont,<>,Hungary; Recsk,Heves,<>,Hungary; Sirok,Heves,<>,Hungary; Somoskoujfalu,Nograd,<>,Hungary; Szirak,Nograd,<>,Hungary; Tarnalelesz,Heves,<>,Hungary; Vanyarc,Nograd,<>,Hungary; Zagyvapalfalva,Nograd,<>,Hungary; Vac,Pest-Pilis-Solt-Kiskun,<>,Hungary; Ketbodony,Nograd,<>,Hungary; Zagyvarona,<>,<>,<>
  The materials were transferred to Yad Vashem by ולריה יוהס
  List of Jews from the Salgotarjan Ghetto who perished during the Holocaust
  The list/s contain approximately 1600 names
- List of Jews from Pelsoc who perished during the Holocaust, 2005-2005; 6 List of murdered Jews Letter Photograph Newspaper clippings List of names xerox; O.41/1007
  List of Jews from Pelsoc who perished during the Holocaust The file also includes photographs, a section from a list from the Yizkor Book containing the names of the Jews of the Pelsoc community who perished, and an article from the "Regioink" newspaper regarding the commemoration of the victims, 1999.
- List of Jews from Kalininskoye, who were murdered, 16/09/1941, Список жителей п.г.т. Калининское, погибших в годы Великой Отечественной войны от рук фашистов 16 сентября 1941 г.; date empty; The file was created by Local Jewish museum; 21 List of murdered Jews xerox; O.41/1025
  Memorials; Kalininskoye,Kalinindorf,Nikolayev,Ukraine (USSR)
  List of Jews from Kalininskoye, who were murdered, 16/09/1941
- List of Jews from Ishkovets who were murdered, 10/1941, 23/06/2005-23/06/2005; 3 List of murdered persons Printout; O.41/981
  Memorials; Killing pits; Escape from the killing pits; Ishkovets,Murovano Kurilovtsy,Vinnitsa,Ukraine (USSR)
  The materials were transferred to Yad Vashem by מר דניביץ*
  List of Jews from Ishkovets who were murdered, 10/1941
- Documentation regarding monuments in memory of Holocaust victims in Eckernfoerde, Tiegenhof and Okunevo, 2004-2004; 15 Poem/song List of survivors Letter Newspaper clippings Survey List of murdered persons xerox; O.41/1005
  Holocaust memory and commemoration; Tiegenhof,Danzig,<>,Danzig; Eckernfoerde,Kiel,Schleswig-Holstein,Germany; Stutthof,Camp
  The materials were transferred to Yad Vashem by רות בן-דוד
  Documentation regarding monuments in memory of Holocaust victims in Eckernfoerde, Tiegenhof and Okunevo Also in the file: - Yiddish translation of the poem "A Futer (Fur Coat)" by Ruth Alperin Ben-Dor.
  - List of Jewish inmates from Stutthof camp who perished and were buried in Eckernfoerde, 05/1945-08/1945, A Jewish Grave and Memorial in the Town of Eckernfoerde; 2004-2004; 1 List of murdered persons; O.41/1005.1
    Eckernfoerde,Kiel,Schleswig-Holstein,Germany; Stutthof,Camp
    List of Jewish inmates from Stutthof camp who perished and were buried in Eckernfoerde, 05/1945-08/1945
  - List of survivors from Stutthof camp whose ship sank on the shores of Eckernfoerde, 05/1945, A Jewish Grave and Memorial in the Town of Echernfoerde; 2004-2004; 1 List of survivors; O.41/1005.2
    List of survivors from Stutthof camp whose ship sank on the shores of Eckernfoerde, 05/1945
- List of Jews from Pczanow who perished during the Holocaust, date empty; 20 List of murdered persons Original; O.41/1017
  Pczanow,Busko,Kielce,Poland
  The materials were transferred to Yad Vashem by שרה נרצי
  List of Jews from Pczanow who perished during the Holocaust
  The list/s contain approximately 748 names
- List of Jews from the Romagna area who were detained in a prison in Ravenna, transferred to a detention center in San Vittore, Milano, deported to Auschwitz, 31/01/1944, and who perished, Rende qui omaggio alla memoria di 28 ebrei vittime dell'odio razziale e delle leggi fasciste; 2007-2007; 6 List of murdered persons List of inmates List of deportees xerox; O.41/1042
  Ravenna,Detention Site,Italy; San Vittore,Detention Site,Italy; Romagna Geo Region,<>,Emilia,Italy; Auschwitz,Camp,Poland
  The materials were transferred to Yad Vashem by לינדה אוטשינסקי
  List of Jews from the Romagna area who were detained in a prison in Ravenna, transferred to a detention center in San Vittore, Milano, deported to Auschwitz, 31/01/1944, and who perished
- Documentation regarding the deportation of Hungarian Jews to camps, including the Dora camp and the sub-camps of the Natzweiler camp, date empty; 533 List of persecuted persons Study Newspaper clippings Testimony Memoirs Diary Letter Legal documentation List of survivors List of inmates List of deportees List of murdered persons xerox; O.41/1081
  Jewish prisoners; Buchenwald,Camp; Natzweiler,Camp; Longwy Thil,Camp; Kochendorf,Camp; Dachau,Camp,Germany; Auschwitz,Camp,Poland; Sachsenhausen,Camp,Germany; Neckar,<>,<>,<>; Neckargartach Heilbronn,Camp; Neckarelz,Camp; Verden,Camp; Uphusen,Camp,Germany; Obernheide,Camp,Germany; Bergen Belsen,Camp,Germany; Dunaszerdahely,Bratislava,Slovakia,Czechoslovakia; Gunskirchen,Camp; Flossenbuerg,Camp; Bremen,Camp,Germany; <>,<>,<>,Hungary; Dora,Camp,Germany; Mauthausen,Camp,Austria
  The materials were transferred to Yad Vashem by Karoly Kengyel
  Documentation regarding the deportation of Hungarian Jews to camps, including the Dora camp and the sub-camps of the Natzweiler camp Also in the file: - Excerpts from research regarding various camps; - Testimonies of survivors; - Excerpts from diaries; - Correspondence of the submitter of the material, Karoly Kengyel, with various archives and institutions; - Lists of those who perished, camp inmates and survivors, mostly from Hungary.
  - List of Jewish inmates in Bergen-Belsen from Dunaszerdahely, with details regarding their fate, Auszug Haeftlingsverzeichnis KZ Bergen-Belsen: Juden aus Dunaszerdahely; date empty; 4 List of inmates; O.41/1081.1
    Dunaszerdahely,Bratislava,Slovakia,Czechoslovakia; Bergen Belsen,Camp,Germany
    List of Jewish inmates in Bergen-Belsen from Dunaszerdahely, with details regarding their fate
  - List of female survivors from Hungary and Poland who were inmates in Auschwitz, Bergen-Belsen, Geisenheim, Neckargerach, Geislingen and Allach camps, date empty; 11 List of inmates List of survivors; O.41/1081.2
    <>,<>,<>,Hungary; <>,<>,<>,Poland; Lodz,Ghetto,Poland; Auschwitz,Camp,Poland; Bergen Belsen,Camp,Germany; Geisenheim,Camp; Geislingen,Camp; Neckargerach,Camp; Allach,Camp,Germany
    List of female survivors from Hungary and Poland who were inmates in Auschwitz, Bergen-Belsen, Geisenheim, Neckargerach, Geislingen and Allach camps
  - Lists of Jews from Hungary who were transferred from Buchenwald to Dora camp, 27-30/05/1944, Neuzugaenge des K.L. Buchenwald vom 27, 28, 29, 30.05.1944; 27/05/1944-30/05/1944; 15 List of inmates; O.41/1081.3
    Buchenwald,Camp; Dora,Camp,Germany; <>,<>,<>,Hungary
    Lists of Jews from Hungary who were transferred from Buchenwald to Dora camp, 27-30/05/1944
    The list/s contain approximately 703 names
  - List of Jews from Hungary who perished in Dora camp, 10/08/1943-03/04/1945, Hungarian Jews who died in concentration camp Dora during the period 10 August 1943 to 3 April 1945; date empty; 10 List of inmates List of murdered persons; O.41/1081.4
    <>,<>,<>,Hungary; Dora,Camp,Germany
    List of Jews from Hungary who perished in Dora camp, 10/08/1943-03/04/1945
  - List of inmates from Hungary in Natzweiler camp and various sub-camps, KL-Natzweiler - detenus hongrois; date empty; 95 List of inmates; O.41/1081.5
    <>,<>,<>,Hungary; Natzweiler,Camp; Auschwitz,Camp,Poland; Dachau,Camp,Germany; Longwy Thil,Camp; Kochendorf,Camp
    List of inmates from Hungary in Natzweiler camp and various sub-camps
    The list/s contain approximately 5403 names
  - List of Yugoslavian inmates, most of them Slovenians from Neckarelz camp, Dokumentation jener Haeftlinge des KZ Neckarelz, die in Nummernbuechern des KZ Natzweiler-Struthof als Jugoslawen eingetragen wurden; date empty; 2 List of inmates; O.41/1081.6
    Neckarelz,Camp
    List of Yugoslavian inmates, most of them Slovenians from Neckarelz camp
  - List of survivors from Achim Uphusen camp, Haeftlinge im Aussenkommando Achim-Uphusen des KZ Neuengamme; date empty; 2 List of inmates List of survivors; O.41/1081.7
    Uphusen,Camp,Germany
    List of survivors from Achim Uphusen camp
  - List of female inmates in Heilbronn camp, 1944, Gefangene Lager-KZ-Zwangsarbeiter Heilbronn 1944; date empty; 2 List of inmates; O.41/1081.8
    Heilbronn,Camp
    List of female inmates in Heilbronn camp, 1944
- List of Jews deported from Prague to Lodz on Transport D, 31/10/1941, date empty; 71 List of deportees Typewritten; O.41/120
  List of Jews deported from Prague to Lodz on Transport D, 31/10/1941
- List of Jews from Gusino who were murdered, 05-06/02/1942, Список расстрелянных мирных жителей п. Гусино, Красненского района Смоленской области 5-6 февраля 1942 года; date empty; 2 List of murdered persons xerox; O.41/963
  Gusino,Krasnoye,Smolensk,Russia (USSR)
  The materials were transferred to Yad Vashem by Farber Isaak
  List of Jews from Gusino who were murdered, 05-06/02/1942
- List of Jewish women from Poland who were prisoners in the Ludwigsdorf forced labor camp, Auszug aus einer Liste - aufgestellt Ludwikowo 01/09/1945; 01/09/1945-01/09/1945; 6 List of camp inmates Typewritten; O.41/133
  Women prisoners; Labor camps; Women; <>,<>,<>,Poland; Ludwigsdorf,Camp,Germany
  List of Jewish women from Poland who were prisoners in the Ludwigsdorf forced labor camp
- Death certificates of the Spierer family from Gyor who perished in the Holocaust and death certificats of Dr. Schossberger and his wife who commited suicide in Novi-Sad in 1944 before being deported to a ghetto, 1976-1976; 8 Personal documents Certification Record of murdered persons Typewritten Handwritten, original; O.41/113
  Gyor,<>,<>,Hungary; Novi Sad,<>,Backa - Vojvodina,Yugoslavia; Auschwitz,Camp,Poland
  The materials were transferred to Yad Vashem by אנגל
  Death certificates of the Spierer family from Gyor who perished in the Holocaust and death certificats of Dr. Schossberger and his wife who commited suicide in Novi-Sad in 1944 before being deported to a ghetto The file also cintains a letter from the submitter of the material with additional details on the Spierers and Schossbergers.
- List of Jewish forced laborers from Poland who perished in the Ludwigsdorf camp, and were buried there, 1942-1944, Lista Żydów pochowanych w Ludwikowie; 07/11/1946-07/11/1946; 4 List of forced laborers List of murdered persons xerox; O.41/130
  Labor camps; Forced labor; Ludwigsdorf,Camp,Germany
  The materials were transferred to Yad Vashem by KONIECZNY ALFRED
  List of Jewish forced laborers from Poland who perished in the Ludwigsdorf camp, and were buried there,1942-1944 The Jews were prisoners in the Ludwigsdorf Forced Labor camp, which was under the charge of the SCHMELT organization Later the camp became a part of the Gross-Rosen camp
- List of Jewish forced laborers in Sopronbanfalva camp who perished, 12/1944-03/1945, Halottak nevsora,Sopronbanfalva; date empty; 6 List of forced laborers List of murdered persons Typewritten; O.41/158
  Sopronbanfalva Camp,Camp,Hungary; MUSZ - munkaszolgalat
  List of Jewish forced laborers in Sopronbanfalva camp who perished, 12/1944-03/1945
  The list/s contain approximately 312 names
- List of Jews from Vranon-nad-Toplou who were deported to the camps, Deportation List of Jews from Vranov n. T. on the date 18 May 1942; 01/01/2004-01/01/2004; 15 List of deportees List of murdered persons xerox; O.41/936
  Vranov nad Toplou,Zemplin,Slovakia,Czechoslovakia; Poprad,Spis,Slovakia,Czechoslovakia
  The materials were transferred to Yad Vashem by סלע מירב
  List of Jews from Vranon-nad-Toplou who were deported to the camps The file also includes: History of the community The file is part of a testimony submitted by Solanik Igor about the history of the Jewish community in Vrana nad Toplou, call number 102-2145 in the Yad Vashem Library
- List of Jews from Liptovsky Svaty Mikulas who perished during the Holocaust, date empty; 7 List of murdered Jews xerox; O.41/150
  Liptovsky Svaty Mikulas,Liptov,Slovakia,Czechoslovakia
  The materials were transferred to Yad Vashem by פרופ' צבי ניר